Don't Let Me Down - Daya&The Chainsmokers
[00:12.99]
Crashing hit a wall
Right now I need a miracle
猛撞上墙
Hurry up now I need a miracle
此时我需要一个奇迹
Stranded reaching out
我急需一个奇迹
I call your name but you're not around
陷入无助的困境
I say your name but you're not around
我呼喊你但你不在身旁
I need you I need you I need you right now
Yeah I need you right now
此刻我需要你
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
I think I'm losing my mind now
不要让我失望
It's in my head darling I hope
我想我已失去理智
That you'll be here when I need you the most
脑海里都是你 我希望
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
当我最需要你的时候你能在我身边
Don't let me down
不要让我失望
Don't let me down down down
Don't let me down
不要让我失望
Don't let me down down down
R r running out of time
不要让我失望
I really thought you were on my side
没有时间了
But now there's nobody by my side
我希望你能在我的身边
I need you I need you I need you right now
但此刻身旁却空无一人
Yeah I need you right now
此刻我需要你
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
I think I'm losing my mind now
不要让我失望
It's in my head darling I hope
我想我已失去理智
That you'll be here when I need you the most
脑海里都是你 我希望
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
当我最需要你的时候你能在我身边
Don't let me down
不要让我失望
Don't let me down down down
Don't let me down don't let me down down down
不要让我失望
Oh I think I'm losing my mind now yeah yeah
不要让我失望 不要让我失望
Oh I think I'm losing my mind now yeah
噢 我想我已失去理智
I need you I need you I need you right now
Yeah I need you right now
此刻我需要你
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
I think I'm losing my mind now
不要让我失望
It's in my head darling I hope
我想我已失去理智
That you'll be here when I need you the most
脑海里都是你 我希望
So don't let me don't let me don't let me down
当我最需要你的时候你能在我身边
Don't let me down
不要让我失望
Yeah don't let me down
Don't let me down oh no oh no
不要让我失望
Said don't let me down
不要让我失望 噢 不要 噢 不要
Don't let me down
说 不要让我失望
Don't let me down down down
不要让我失望
[03:19.25]